<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<QAItems>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>How can I make the process faster next time?</Question>
        <Answer><![CDATA[Click <a href="event:EligibilityForm">here</a> to print out the employee eligibility form and include it with your new hire application paperwork.  This will provide you with more time to complete the application for tax credit the next time you hire a new employee.]]></Answer>
    </QAItem>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>Why does Intuit need Power of Attorney?</Question>
        <Answer><![CDATA[Power of Attorney allows Intuit to apply for tax credit on your behalf and is required in order to provide Tax Credit Service.  Specific instructions will be provided in your application for tax credit.]]></Answer>
    </QAItem>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>What is the 8850 form?</Question>
        <Answer><![CDATA[The 8850 is one of the official forms required by the state workforce agencies to process your tax credit application.  This form must be signed by your employee.]]></Answer>
    </QAItem>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>What is a DD214, Discharge Papers or FL 21-802?</Question>
        <Answer><![CDATA[DD Form 214 or Discharge Papers refers to a Certificate of Release or Discharge from Active Duty and is issued upon a military service member's retirement, separation or discharge from active-duty military.  The FL 21-802 is issued by the Department of Veteran Affairs and certifies a Veteran with a service connected disability.]]></Answer>
    </QAItem>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>What is a SNAP benefit history, SNAP award letter?</Question>
        <Answer><![CDATA[A copy of your employee's SNAP benefits history is a document they should have that describes the benefits they have received from SNAP.  Alternatively, you can send in a signed statement with a description of the benefits received and during what months they were received along with their case number ID.  More specific instructions are be provided in your application for tax credit.]]></Answer>
    </QAItem>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>What is a self attestation?</Question>
        <Answer><![CDATA[The self attestation is a document signed by your employee that authenticates that what they have stated is true and factual.  More detailed instructions will be provided in your application for tax credit.]]></Answer>
    </QAItem>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>What is a SSI Record or SSI Authorization?</Question>
        <Answer><![CDATA[Either of these documents provide proof that the employee was authorized to receive social security benefits or has already received them.  More detailed instructions will be provided in your application for tax credit.]]></Answer>
    </QAItem>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>What is a Conditional Certification from a State Workforce Agency?</Question>
        <Answer><![CDATA[An individual who has received, prior to being hired, a conditional certification from a state workforce agency or participating local agency will have provided this document to you as part of their employment application.  More detailed instructions will be provided in your application for tax credit.]]></Answer>
    </QAItem>
</QAItems>