<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<QAItems>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>What are Employer Tax Credits and how much can I save?</Question>
        <Answer><![CDATA[The Federal Work Opportunity Tax Credit (WOTC) program was devised to help improve neighborhoods, employ disadvantaged workers and stimulate business growth through tax incentives.  All employers regardless of location or industry qualify for WOTC.  The program allows you to potentially claim as much as $9,000.00 in income tax credit per eligible employee you hire.]]></Answer>
    </QAItem>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>How does Employer Tax Credit Services work?</Question>
        <Answer><![CDATA[Intuit Employer Tax Credit Services helps you identify, apply for, and potentially receive income tax credit each time you hire an eligible employee.<sup>*</sup>  These tax credits can be used to lower your income tax liability dollar for dollar. If either your corporation or a shareholder has a tax liability, the tax credit is a dollar for dollar offset.  For example, if either your corporation or a shareholder owes $10,000.00 in Federal Income Tax and has a Work Opportunity Tax Credit of $6,000.00, the estimated income tax payment can be reduced to $4,000.00. All you have to do is apply in 3 easy steps each time you hire an employee.  We'll keep you informed about progress and deliver your tax credit to you in time to potentially reduce your quarterly estimated income tax payments.  At the end of the year we'll provide you with a tax schedule you can take to your tax preparer so that they can include your tax credit with your annual income tax return.  Have questions? Email taxcredits@intuit.com or Call M-F 8am-5pm PT 800.422.8800, ext. 82270.<br><br><br><font size="10">*A company who hires an employee that qualifies under the Long Term Temporary Assistance for Needy Families (TANF) category and employs them continuously over a two year period is eligible for the maximum Federal Income tax credit of $9,000.00.  Eligibility can be determined for free using our Online Eligibility Form.  Your employee must work at least 120 hours for you to receive any tax credit, but the more time they work for you the larger your tax credit will grow.  If your employee quits or is terminated before they've worked 120 hours, you may not receive any tax credit.</font>]]> </Answer>
    </QAItem>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>Why haven't I heard of this before?</Question>
        <Answer><![CDATA[Large or public companies routinely take advantage of hiring tax credits, but small to medium sized business owners miss out on money when they don't take advantage of these programs. Intuit Employer Tax Credit Services makes it easy for you to get hiring tax credits &#8212; income tax credits you're legally entitled to!]]></Answer>
    </QAItem>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>How does this relate to the HIRE Act?</Question>
        <Answer><![CDATA[Work Opportunity Tax Credit (WOTC) and HIRE Act exemption are competing tax credits and cannot both be claimed.  However, if you forego the HIRE Act exemption and move forward with the WOTC tax credit you're still eligible to receive the HIRE Act retention bonus of $1,000.00 if you retain the employee for more than 1 year. To proceed with the WOTC tax credit and HIRE Act retention bonus, call an Intuit Tax Credit Specialist for a 1:1 consultation M-F 8am-5pm PT 800.422.8800, ext. 82270 or email us at taxcredits@intuit.com. If you don't qualify for the WOTC tax credit or you'd like to learn more about the HIRE Act exemption, click <a href="event:hireactinformation">here</a>.]]></Answer>
    </QAItem>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>How much does it cost and how will I be charged?</Question>
        <Answer>Intuit will help you determine eligibility and apply for tax credit for free. You and your employee will be asked some questions to determine if you qualify. If you do, we'll provide a pre-filled application you can electronically sign and return to Intuit. If your application is approved, and your employee works a minimum 120 hours, you'll be charged ${price} on January 25th -- otherwise you pay nothing.  Minimum tax credit amount is $217.50, based on an employee paid minimum wage ($7.25/hr) that qualifies under the least lucrative tax credit category and that only works 120 hours for your company. Maximum tax credits range by qualification category from $1,200 to up to $9,000. The longer the employee works for you the larger the tax credit.</Answer>
    </QAItem>
    <QAItem>
        <Question>How much work will I have to do?</Question>
        <Answer>Applying for your tax credit through our service is quick and easy. You can either determine eligibility yourself using this web site or you can call an Intuit Tax Credit Specialist for a 1:1 consultation M-F 8am-5pm PT 800.422.8800, ext. 82270. If eligible, electronically sign the application within 23 days of your new employee's hire date to comply with the Federal application deadline. We can't process any application signed after this date and your tax credit may expire. Have More Questions? Email taxcredits@intuit.com or call M-F 8am-5pm PT 800.422.8800, ext. 82270</Answer>
    </QAItem>
</QAItems>
